Guide to the National Coalition for Haitian Rights Records, 1964-2020, bulk 1982-2004 RL.11314
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Print Materials, 1935-2008, undated; bulk 1980-2006; 1
  - Newsletters, Bulletins and Other Periodical Publications, 1979-2000, undated; 2
    - Haitian News & Resource Service, 1994 (Box 176)
    - Haitian News & Resource Service, 1994 (Box 176)
    - Haitian News & Resource Service, 1994 (Box 176)
    - Haitian News & Resource Service, 1995 (Box 176)
    - Haitian News & Resource Service, 1995 (Box 177)
    - Haitian News & Resource Service, 1995 (Box 177)
    - Haitian News & Resource Service, 1996 (Box 177)
    - Haitian News & Resource Service, summary edition, 1992 (Box 177)
    - Haitian News & Resource Service, summary edition, 1992 (Box 177)
    - Haitian News & Resource Service, summary edition, 1992 (Box 177)
    - Haitian News & Resource Service, summary edition, 1992 (Box 177)
    - Haitian News & Resource Service, summary edition, 1992 (Box 177)
    - Haitian News & Resource Service, summary edition, 1993 (Box 177)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1993 (Box 177)
    - Haitian Studies Association Newsletter, 1990 (Box 177)
    - Haitian Studies Association Newsletter, 1991 (Box 177)
    - Haitians in NY awareness movement, undated (Box 177)
    - Haitians Moving Towards Forming National Community Action Networks, Haitian-American Conference Planning Committee, 1996 (Box 177)
    - HCDI Newsletter, Vol 1.2, 1996 (Box 178)
    - Health + Human Rights, an International Quarterly Journal, vol. 2, No. 2, 1997 (Box 178)
    - Heritage Foundation "Is Haiti turning into another Cuba?", 1991 (Box 178)
    - History of the Immigration and Refugee services of America network, 1998 (Box 178)
    - Human rights bulletins from Haiti (binder), 1989-1991 (Box 178)
    - Human Rights Observer, 1990-1992 (Box 178)
    - Human Rights training program in Haiti reports, 1995-1996 (Box 178)
    - Immigrant Policy News, 1996-1997 (Box 178)
    - Immigration Briefs, 1990-1992 (Box 178)
    - Immigration Newsletter, 1992 (Box 178)
    - Immigration Newsletter, 1986-1991 (Box 178)
    - Information Bulletin, 1990-1992 (Box 178)
    - Information Libre, 1990-1994 (Box 178)
    - Information Libre (Vol. IX, No. 92-94), 1994 (Box 178)
    - Information Libre, pour une commission de la verite en Haiti booklet, 1994 (Box 178)
    - Institutionalizing Human Rights in Haiti, undated (Box 178)
    - InterAction, American Council for Voluntary International Action, 1996 (Box 178)
    - Inter-American Commission on Human Rights Annual Report, 1982 (Box 178)
    - International Catholic Migration Commission annual report, 1993 (Box 178)
    - International Commission of Jurists, the Review, 1980 (Box 178)
    - International Council on Social Welfare (ICSW)- World Summit on Social Development, 1995 (Box 178)
    - International Peace Academy, 1996-1998 (Box 179)
    - International Policy Report, 1997 (Box 179)
    - Interpreter Releases: report and analysis of immigration and nationality law, 1990-1996 (Box 179)
    - Ki Jan aparey Jistis la Fonksyone (How the Justice System Works), 1990 (Box 179)
    - Konakom Suley Leve Vol. 3 No. 1, 1991 (Box 179)
    - La Isla, 1995 (Box 179)
    - LAICS Engages (religious bulletin), 1990 (Box 179)
    - L'Artibonite, 1987-1991 (Box 179)
    - Lavalas Pou Ayiti (News for Haiti), 1993 (Box 179)
    - Le Moniteur, 1979 (Box 179)
    - Le Moniteur, 1983 (Box 179)
    - Le Moniteur, 1986 (Box 179)
    - Le Moniteur, 1989 (Box 179)
    - Le Moniteur, 1990 (Box 179)
    - Le Noveau Petit Impartial Vol. 2 No. 4, 1991 (Box 179)
    - Le Regard, 1980 (Box 179)
    - Legalization/Adjustment: AFL-CIO Brochures, 1987 (Box 179)
    - Liaison, 1991 (Box 179)
    - Liaison Bulletin, 1994 (Box 179)
    - Libete, Ane 2, Nos 51-54, 1993 (Box 179)
    - Libete, Vol 1., No. 35-36, 1991 (Box 179)
    - Libete,Vol. 2, Nos 94-97, 1992 (Box 179)
    - Lutheran Immigration & Refugee Service information on Haitian developments, 1995 (Box 179)
    - Manuel a l 'intention des immigrants haitiens, 1991 (Box 179)
    - Millions of Haitians Have No Voice Brochure, undated (Box 179)
    - Monday - Vol. 9 No. 11, 1990 (Box 179)
    - National Decree on the Functioning of the National Penitentiary Administration, 1989 (Box 179)
    - National Labor Committee, 1996 (Box 180)
    - National Peace and Justice Commission bulletin, no. 56, 1992 (Box 180)
    - NCHR Public Statements, 1990-1991 (Box 180)
    - NCHR Haiti Office activities report, 1993-1994 (Box 180)
    - NCHR internal reports, 1998-1999 (Box 180)
    - NCHR join slogan with pictures, undated (Box 180)
    - NCHR Press release and briefing paper translation, 1997 (Box 180)
    - NCHR Press Releases, 1994 (Box 180)
    - NCHR Press Releases and Statements, 2000 (Box 180)
    - NCHR Public Statements, 1994 (Box 180)
    - NCHR Public Statements, 1999-2000 (Box 180)
    - NCHR publications and brochures, undated (Box 180)
    - NCHR Quarterly Reports, 1993-1995 (Box 180)
    - NCHR releases, 1988, undated (Box 180)
    - NCHR report on program activities during 1991, 1992 (Box 180)
    - NCHR reports from Port-au-Prince Office, 1994-1995 (Box 180)
    - NCHR Statement, City Hall, 1991 (Box 180)
    - NCHR/Human Rights Watch America press releases, 1994-1995 (Box 180)
    - Neighborhood Housing Services, 1996, undated (Box 181)
    - News from Americas Watch / NCHR, 1992 (Box 181)
    - ONG, Groupes de base et democratie en Haiti, 1992 (Box 181)
    - Peace & Democracy, 1994 (Box 181)
    - Perspectives Haiti bulletins, 1992-1994 (Box 181)
    - Premier Rapport Annuel d'Activites de L'Office de la Protection du Citoyen, 1997-1998 (Box 181)
    - Press Release from Prime Minister Rene Preval, 1991 (Box 181)
    - Promoting a Comprehensive Refugee and Migration Policy, undated (Box 181)
    - Publications, 1985-1989; (1 of 2) (Box 181)
    - Publications, 1985-1989; (2 of 2) (Box 181)
    - Refugee Reports, 1995 (Box 181)
    - Refugee Reports, 1996 (Box 181)
    - Refugee Reports Vol. 14 No. 1, 1993 (Box 181)
    - Report on Haiti Elections- Network News, 1991 (Box 181)
    - Reports by Pierre Esperance, 1994 (Box 181)
    - Sa K'Pase newsletters, 1992 (Box 181)
    - Status Report: USAID/Haiti Economic Recovery Program, 1995 (Box 181)
    - The Advisor, 1989 (Box 181)
    - The Carter Center promotional materials and newsletters, 1988, undated (Box 181)
    - The Dominican Republic and Haiti in route towards the year 2000 (Box 181)
      [French] [Spanish]
    - The Haiti Beat, Vol. 4, No3., 1990 (Box 181)
    - The Haiti News, 1994 (Box 182)
    - The Haitian Register, 2002 (Box 182)
    - The Journals of the Strategic Reflection Group (GR 5) No. 1, 2004 (Box 182)
    - The National Context, 1995 (Box 182)
    - The Ned Backgrounder vol. 1 no. 2, 1992 (Box 182)
    - The Unregulated Internationalization of the Economy and the North American Free Trade Agreement, 1993 (Box 182)
    - UN and OAS Human Rights Updates, 1993 (Box 182)
    - UN PARinAC conference, 1993 (Box 182)
    - UNICEF ad on mothers, undated (Box 182)
    - Universal Declaration of Human Rights, 1993 (Box 182)
    - Urgent appeals protest letters, 1992-1993 (Box 182)
    - Washington Office on Haiti Report on Human Rights violations under Aristide, 1991 (Box 182)
    - Washington Office on Haiti urgent action + press releases, 1985-1992 (Box 182)
    - Washington Office on Latin America summary + press, 1995, undated (Box 182)
    - What you need to know about becoming an American citizen, undated (Box 182)
    - Women's commission for refugee women and children Newsletter, 1991 (Box 182)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1989 (Box 184)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1989 (Box 184)
  - Press, 1986-2008, undated; 3
    - "Despite a Generous Spirit", 1986 (Box 182)
    - "Double take on the Haitian Refugee Immigration Fairness Act," Jocelyn McCalla, Haitian Times, 1999 (Box 182)
    - "Haiti- Human Rights in Shreds", 1993 (Box 182)
    - "On the Horns of a Dilemma", 1994 (Box 182)
    - "The Haitian Revolution of 1990" (Box 182)
    - "The Littlest Slaves in Haiti" Report on Restaveks by Debbie Sontag, Miami Herald, 1990 (Box 182)
    - Agence Haitienne de Presse (resumes de nouvelles nationales), 1992 (Box 182)
    - Agence Haitienne de Presse (resumes de nouvelles nationales), 1992 (Box 182)
    - Agence Haitienne de Presse (resumes de nouvelles nationales), 1991; (1 of 3) (Box 182A)
    - Agence Haitienne de Presse (resumes de nouvelles nationales), 1991; (2 of 3) (Box 182A)
    - Agence Haitienne de Presse (resumes de nouvelles nationales), 1991; (3 of 3) (Box 182A)
    - Agence Haitienne de Presse (resumes de nouvelles nationales), 1992 (Box 183)
    - Agence Haitienne de Presse (resumes de nouvelles nationales), 1992 (Box 183)
    - Agence Haitienne de Presse releases, 1992-1993 (Box 183)
    - Amnesty International action plan on the arrest of President Aristide's supporters, 1991 (Box 183)
    - Articles on Haiti, 1994 (Box 183)
    - Articles to Haiti en Marche, 1994 (Box 183)
    - Condemnation of killing of political opponents of military junta, 1991 (Box 183)
    - Creation of a entity in US to raise funds and provide assistance to communities, 1991 (Box 183)
    - Deportation relief, 1997-1999 (Box 183)
    - Elections in Haiti Reports (including some press), 1995 (Box 183)
    - Francophone News Sources, 1996 (Box 183)
    - Haiti en Marche, vol. VIII, No. 10+12, 1994 (Box 183)
    - Haiti Lumiere, Vol. 1, No. 10, 1989 (Box 183)
    - Haiti Observateur, 1987 (Box 183)
    - Haiti Observateur, 1988-1989 (Box 183)
    - Haiti Observateur, 1994 (Box 183)
    - Haiti Progres, Vol. 12, No. 4, 6, 8, 1994 (Box 184)
    - Haiti Progres, vol. 9, No.20-21, 26, 1991 (Box 184)
    - Haiti Progres, vol. 5, No. 8, 13-14, 1987 (Box 184)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1989 (Box 184)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1989 (Box 184)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1989 (Box 184)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1990 (Box 184)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1990 (Box 184)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1990 (Box 184)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1990-1991 (Box 184)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1991 (Box 185)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1991 (Box 185)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1991 (Box 185)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1991 (Box 185)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1991 (Box 185)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1991 (Box 185)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1991 (Box 185)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1991 (Box 185)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1991 (Box 185)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1991 (Box 185)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1991 (Box 185)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1992 (Box 186)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1993 (Box 186)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1994 (Box 186)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1994 (Box 186)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1994 (Box 186)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1995 (Box 186)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1995 (Box 186)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1996 (Box 186)
    - Haitian News and Resource Service, 1996 (Box 186)
    - Haitian Times, 2008 (Box 187)
    - History of Haiti LA Times, Bella Stumbo, 1991 (Box 187)
    - History of politics and corruption, 1986 (Box 187)
    - Human Rights clippings, 1994 (Box 187)
    - Human Rights violations in Haiti and Haitian refugees, 1992 (Box 187)
    - Human Rights violations under Aristide, 1991 (Box 187)
    - Immigration Bills, news, 1996 (Box 187)
    - Immigration/refugee articles, 1994 (Box 187)
    - Le Matin, 1991 (Box 187)
    - Le Matin, 1991 (Box 187)
    - Le Nouvelliste, 1987 (Box 187)
    - Le Nouvelliste, 1991 (Box 187)
    - Le Nouvelliste, 1991 (Box 187)
    - Le Nouvelliste, 1991 (Box 187)
    - Le Nouvelliste, Dec 30 1993 - Jan 2, 1994 (Box 153)
      Cover includes political cartoon by Dodard [French]
    - Le Petit Samedi Soir, 1988 (Box 187)
    - Letter on Bush administration's reaction to the coup, 1991 (Box 187)
    - Library Files, 1995 (Box 187)
    - L'Union, 1991 (Box 188)
    - Miscellaneous articles, 2000, 2004 (Box 188)
    - Miscellaneous news, 1989-1994, undated (Box 188)
    - NCHR: News stories through email correspondence, 2000 (Box 188)
    - New York Newsday Interview with Jocelyn McCalla and Raymond Joseph, undated (Box 188)
    - New York Times, 1991-1994 (Box 188)
    - News Articles on Haiti, 1988 (Box 188)
    - News Articles on Haiti, 1993-1994 (Box 188)
    - News Articles on Haiti, 1996-1997 (Box 188)
    - News Articles on Haiti, 1999-2000 (Box 188)
    - News clips via Internet on Haiti, 1999 (Box 188)
    - Newspapers on the situation in Haiti days after the coup, 1991 (Box 188)
    - Press, 1994 (Box 188)
    - Press, 1997 (Box 189)
    - Press, 1997 (Box 189)
    - Press, 1997 (Box 189)
    - Press, 1998 (Box 189)
    - Press, 1998 (Box 189)
    - Press (1/2), 1997; (1 of 2) (Box 189)
    - Press (2/2), 1997; (2 of 2) (Box 189)
    - Press (Norman L. Zucker), 1997 (Box 189)
    - Press (Reverend Dick Wildeman), 1997 (Box 189)
    - Press release on Pierre (KOSMIKA farmers) arrest, 1991 (Box 189)
    - Press releases, 1985-1991 (Box 207)
    - Press releases, 1992-1993 (Box 207)
    - Press releases, 1996-2004 (Box 207)
    - Press reports on refugee and press freedom, 1993 (Box 189)
    - Sifting Through Haiti's Past- Anne Christine d'Adesky Magazine Feature, 1991 (Box 189)
    - Soho Press, 1994 (Box 189)
    - Statement on the evacuation of Evans Paul (Port-au-Prince mayor), 1994 (Box 189)
    - Sunshine (reprinted from the Ft. Lauderdale News/Sun Sentinel), 1986 (Box 189)
    - The Chronicle of Philanthropy, Vol. IX, No. 21, 1997 (Box 189)
    - The Real Columbus: Sugar and Slavery in Latin America, 1992 (Box 190)
    - Violence in Gervais AP news brief, 1991 (Box 190)
    - Voices of Haiti's Popular Movement, 1994 (Box 190)
    - Weber-Haiti Photo Shoot, 2003 (Box 190)
    - Wire communications on Haiti Embargo, 1993; (1 of 2) (Box 190)
    - Wire communications on Haiti Embargo, 1993; (2 of 2) (Box 190)
    - Wire stories, Human Rights, 1993 (Box 190)
  - Reports, 1935-2006, undated; 4
    - A Few Facts and Reflections about Haiti, Haitian Immigrants in New York and some other concerns, 1991 (Box 191)
    - A Food Aid Strategy for Haiti: Maximizing Development Effectiveness, 1987 (Box 191)
    - A Proposed Rural Credit Strategy: Should USAID/Haiti Fund New Rural Credit Project?, 1987 (Box 191)
    - A Report on NCHR Activities in 1993 (Box 191)
    - A Report on NCHR Activities in 1995 (Box 191)
    - A Report on the 4th Annual Peacekeeping Mission, United Nations Missions in Haiti, 1995 (Box 191)
    - A Report on the New York Public Hearing on the Rights of the Undocumented Immigrants and Refugees in NYC, 1985 (Box 191)
    - A Study of Police in new communities, 1992 (Box 191)
    - A Troubled Year: Haitians in the Dominican Republic, Americas Watch/NCHR, 1992 (Box 191)
    - A Woman's Guide to AIDS, NYC Department of Health, 1992 (Box 191)
    - Actualites, Americas Watch/NCHR, 1989 (Box 191)
    - Advocacy Matters articles, 1994 (Box 191)
    - Advocating for a military intervention in Haiti, 1994 (Box 191)
    - African and Haitian Refugees, 1989 (Box 191)
    - Agence Haitienne de Presse partial list of cases of aggression against the press, 1993 (Box 191)
    - Aid Program for the relief of poverty, 1994 (Box 191)
    - AIDS and the Third World, 1987 (Box 191)
    - AIDS Treatment Registry Inc., 1990 (Box 191)
    - American Immigration Law Foundation practice advisories and updates, 1996 (Box 191)
    - Americas Watch/NCHR, "Half the Story: the Skewed US Monitoring of Repatriated Haitian Refugees", 1992 (Box 191)
    - Americas Watch: The Current Situation in Haiti, Testimony of Michael S. Hooper, House Subcommittee on Western Hemisphere Affairs, 1987 (Box 191)
    - Amnesty International Briefing, 1985 (Box 191)
    - Amnesty International call for action on continuing human right violations, 1992 (Box 192)
    - Amnesty International Haiti Human Rights and the Bicentennial, 2004 (Box 192)
    - Amnesty International Haiti Briefing, 1985 (Box 192)
    - Amnesty International Haiti - Justice and liberty in peril again, 2000 (Box 192)
    - Amnesty International, Ayiti - "Kwape espiral lavyolans: Yon denye chans pou Ayiti?", 2004 (Box 192)
    - Amnesty International, Haiti - Deaths in Detention, Torture and Inhumane Prison Conditions, 1987 (Box 192)
    - Amnesty International, Haiti - Human Rights Held Ransom (with French translation), 1992 (Box 192)
    - Amnesty International, Mozambique Peacekeeping materials, 1994 (Box 192)
    - Amnesty International, Peacekeeping & Human Rights, 1994 (Box 192)
    - Analysis of the Haitian Justice System, 1994 (Box 192)
    - Anti-Slavery Society for Human Rights: Migrant Workers in the Dominican Republic, 1979-1982 (Box 192)
    - Aristide government's human rights record, 1991 (Box 192)
    - Ayiti, 1991 (Box 192)
    - Basic Law Manual: Asylum Summary & Overview Concerning Asylum Law, 1991 (Box 192)
    - Because I am More, 1989 (Box 192)
    - Behind the Mountains, 1990 (Box 192)
    - Beyond the Bateyes - NCHR, 1996 (Box 192)
    - Black Leaders' Support for Haitians packet (1/2), 1976-1979; (1 of 2) (Box 192)
    - Black Leaders' Support for Haitians packet (2/2), 1976-1979; (2 of 2) (Box 192)
    - Blaise - Haitian Press Agency National Current Events Feb-Dec 1990, (1 of 3) (Box 193)
    - Blaise- Haitian Press Agency National Current Events Feb-Dec 1990, (2 of 3) (Box 193)
    - Blaise- Haitian Press Agency National Current Events Feb-Dec 1990, (3 of 3) (Box 193)
    - Blaise reports notes, 1989; (1 of 2) (Box 193)
    - Blaise reports notes, 1989; (2 of 2) (Box 193)
    - Can Haiti's Police Reforms Be Sustained?, 1998 (Box 193)
    - Caribbean Human Rights Network Report- Refugee situation in Belize, 1992 (Box 193)
    - CARLI program hotline for victims of human rights violations annual report, 2004-2005 (Box 194)
    - Carnegie Commission on Preventing Deadly Conflict, 1997-1998 (Box 194)
    - CEDH- "A Zone of no Rights", 2005 (Box 194)
    - Cen. Lafontant Joseph report, 1991 (Box 194)
    - Center for Preventive Action, Fourth Annual Conference: Progress and Pitfalls in Preventive Action, 1997 (Box 194)
    - CHRC L-HR Report: Haitian Refugee Interdiction, 1994 (Box 194)
    - Chronology of NCHR activities and reports, 1987-1995 (Box 194)
    - Church World Service reports, 1995 (Box 194)
    - Citizens Collective report on Haitian electoral crisis, undated (Box 194)
    - Comite de Coordination de las Instituciones Haitianas reports, 1991-1995 (Box 194)
    - Commission de Verite, Haiti, Claudette Werleigh talks in Geneva, 1996 (Box 194)
    - Commission Justice et Paix reports on human rights violations, 1991 (Box 194)
    - Communal Governance Program, Demobilization & Reintegration Programme Monthly Report, 1996 (Box 194)
    - Community Development Resource Guide, undated (Box 194)
    - Compilation of recorded violations from 1993 (Box 194)
    - Comptes-rendus des visites effectuees aupres des ONG dominicaines du 20 au 29 avril 1999 (Box 194)
    - Concert for Haiti, 1995 (Box 194)
    - Conditions at Krome North Processing Center, 1991; (1 of 2) (Box 195)
    - Conditions at Krome North Processing Center, 1991; (2 of 2) (Box 195)
    - Congressional Reports on Interdiction, 1981 (Box 195)
    - Cornell-Haitian Boat Interdiction and Return, 1993 (Box 195)
    - Costa Rica - Nicaragua Migrant Labor report, 1993 (Box 195)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, reports prepared for third annual conference for Center for Preventive Action, 1996 (Box 195)
    - Country Reports on Human Rights Practices for 1981, 1982 (Box 195)
    - Credit Report on Haiti (Partial Manuscript), undated (Box 195)
    - Conflict Transformation by Peaceful Means manual, 1998 (Box 195)
    - Demobilization of the Haitian armed forces, 1996 (Box 195)
    - Department of State Report on Haiti, 1991 (Box 195)
    - Destruction of Civil Society in Haiti, 1993 (Box 195)
    - Diagnosis on the Socio-Judicial Reality of the Dominican-Haitian Families Living in the DR, 1994 (Box 195)
    - Directory of Haitianists, 1994 (Box 195)
    - Discours du Aristide, 46th Session of the United Nations General Assembly, 1991 (Box 195)
    - Dominican Republic ban Creole radio program and crack down on protesters, 1992 (Box 195)
    - Dominican Republic Prelim Report to GSP, 1991 (Box 195)
    - Droits de l'homme, les droits de l'enfant, 1990 (Box 195)
    - Duvalierism since Duvalier, NCHR/Americas Watch, 1986 (Box 195)
    - Elections 2000: Participatory Democracy in Haiti," by Melinda Miles, 2001 (Box 196)
    - Elections 84 a la Duvalier: un rapport sur les Droits de l'Homme a partir d'une Mission d'Enquete, 1984 (Box 196)
    - Electoral law pamphlets (Haiti), 1987 (Box 196)
    - Eleksyon Ayiti 87, C.E.P., 1987 (Box 196)
    - End US aid to Haiti, 1987 (Box 196)
    - Entre Mas Cambian Las Cosas… Derechos Humanos en Haiti, 1989 (Box 196)
    - Environment and Development in Haiti, 1993 (Box 196)
    - Escalating Repression in Haiti and the Failure of US Policy, 1992 (Box 196)
    - Estimation of the total population of 18 year olds and older, 1986 (Box 196)
    - Examples of repression and torture since military coup in Haiti booklet, 1993 (Box 196)
      [translated in English, Spanish, French and Kreyol]
    - Exhumations in Panama, 1990 (Box 196)
    - Expulsion of Haitian refugees since the coup, 1991 (Box 196)
    - First Partial Review of the Repression Under St. Marc, 1991 (Box 196)
    - Florida Rural Legal Services of Miami, 1995 (Box 196)
    - FNC Canada, 1987-1988 (Box 196)
    - Forced Labor in Sugar Industry, 1991 (Box 196)
    - From Chains Against Liberty, 1993 (Box 196)
    - From Haiti Commission "On the Dominican/Haitian Frontier", 1991 (Box 196)
    - From Repression to Detention, 1993 (Box 196)
    - Fugitives from Injustice: The Crisis of Internal Displacement in Haiti, Human Rights Watch report, 1994 (Box 196)
    - GAO report on organization of American States, 1992 (Box 196)
    - Getting Started: A Guidebook for Immigrants in New York, 1992 (Box 196)
    - GHRAP- Conjuncture Analysis, 1989 (Box 197)
    - GHRAP: Haiti: Crises and Alternatives, 1986-1987 (Box 197)
    - GHRAP: Struggles Against Unstable Politics, 1987-1988 (Box 197)
    - GHRAP: The Affirmation of A Political Transition, 1989 (Box 197)
    - GHRAP: The Force Coup of Nov. 29,1987 (Box 197)
    - Global Focus: A New Foreign Policy Agenda, 1997 (Box 197)
    - Governance and human rights violation, 1992 (Box 197)
    - Government of Haiti: Truth Commission, 1995 (Box 197)
    - Habeas Corpus for Haitians seeking asylum, 1986 (Box 197)
    - Haiti and Human Rights reports, 1999-2000 (Box 197)
    - Haiti and the New World Order, 1994 (Box 197)
    - Haiti Bank's Transition Strategy, 2005-2006 (Box 197)
    - Haiti Democratic Needs Assistance, 1989 (Box 197)
    - Haiti Disaster Relief Committee preliminary financial progress report, 1998 (Box 197)
    - Haiti election report, 1990 (Box 197)
    - Haiti elections watch, 1990 (Box 197)
    - Haiti Human Rights Violations: October 1980-October 1981, Amnesty International release (Box 197)
    - Haiti National Police Instruction Manual, 1995-1996 (Box 197)
    - Haiti programme d'urgence pour le soulagement de la pauvrete, 1994 (Box 198)
    - Haiti- Project Paper Targeted Watershed Management, 1991; (1 of 2) (Box 198)
    - Haiti- Project Paper Targeted Watershed Management, 1991; (2 of 2) (Box 198)
    - Haiti- Security compromised, 1995 (Box 198)